Guide to President's Office (Richard M. Turner) Records 1972-1990
Lane Community College
President's Office (Richard M. Turner) Records
1972-1990
Lane Community College (Eugene, Or.) Archives 4000 East 30th Avenue Eugene, Oregon 97405 Phone: 541-463-5466 Fax: 541-463-3996 E-mail: archives@lanecc.edu Web: http://www.lanecc.edu/archives/
A-039
Lane Community College. President's Office
25.2 cubic feet 63 document boxes
Correspondence, subject files, and administrative records documenting the tenure of Richard M. Turner, president of Lane Community College, 1985-1988.
Richard Martin Turner is a native of Charleston, South Carolina. He received a bachelor’s degree from Fisk University in Nashville, Tennessee, in 1956; a master’s degree in music education from Indiana University in 1961; and a doctorate in music education from Indiana University in 1972.
He began his academic career at Stillman College in Tuscaloosa, Alabama, where he was an associate professor of music and chair of the Department of Music (1956-1968). From 1968-1971 he was chairman of the Department of Music at Fisk University. Fisk University awarded him an honorary doctor of humane letters in 1980.
He began his career in community college administration at the Community College of Baltimore in Maryland; he served as dean of student activities, dean of faculty, and provost, 1971-1979. He served as president of South Central Community College in New Haven, Connecticut, 1979-1985.
Turner was president of Lane Community College, 1985-1988.
He was president of the Nashville Technical Institute in Nashville, Tennessee, 1988-91. From 1992-1996, he served as campus dean, provost, interim president, and executive vice-president at Wayne County Community College District in Detroit, Michigan. He was president of Turner Associates Mentors, Inc. from1966-2004. Since 2004, he has been interim president of Baltimore City Community College.
The collection contains the correspondence, subject files, and administrative records documenting the tenure of college president Richard M. Turner, 1985-1988. The collection documents the activities of the president including his dealings with departments, programs, and committees as well as his participation and involvement with organizations outside of the college. The collection also includes Turner's speeches and writings.
The collection contains the correspondence and administrative records documenting the tenure of college president Richard M. Turner, 1985-1988. The collection is divided into five series:
1. Correspondence, 1982 – 1989
2. Internal Organizations - College Departments, Committees, and Subject Files, 1972 – 1990
3. External Organizations, 1973 – 1989
4. Speeches and Writings, 1982 – 1988
5. Legal Records, 1983 - 1989
Collection is open for research with the exception of legal records.
Records were transferred from the President's Office to the college archives in seven accessions between 1988 and 2004
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Turner, Richard M.; Aspinwall-Lamberts, Julie; Belcher, Jacque; Carter, John E. (Jack); Hillier, Richard; Matsen, Marie; Warford, Larry
Lane Community College (Eugene, Or.) President's Office; Oregon Community College Association; League for Innovation in the Community College
Oregon; Eugene (Or.)
Universities and colleges--Administration; Universities and colleges--Oregon; Lane Community College--Administration; College presidents--Oregon; Community college presidents--Oregon; Community colleges--Administration--Oregon; Community colleges--Oregon
Colleges and universities
Oregon; Eugene (Or.)
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
Folder label descriptions with dates are followed by the box/folder number.
- Correspondence, 1982-1989; 4.0 cubic feet, 10 document boxes
  This series contains chronological correspondence, as well as correspondence to and from college administrators: Julie Aspinwall-Lamberts, director of Institutional Research, Planning and Evaluation; Jacque Belcher, vice president for instruction; Jack Carter, vice president for student services and interim president following Turner; Richard Hillier, vice president for administrative services; and Larry Warford, assistant to the president.
  Collection is open to the public.
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically and also alphabetically by name of correspondent.
  - Correspondence, Chronological, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 1/1-7/7)
  - Correspondence, Julie Aspinwall-Lamberts, Director of Institutional Research, Planning and Evaluation, 1986 -1987 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Correspondence, Jacque Belcher, Vice-President for Instruction, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 7/9-12, 8/1-4)
  - Correspondence, John (Jack) Carter, Vice President for Student Services, Interim President, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 8/5-7)
  - Correspondence, Richard Hillier, Vice President for Administrative Services, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/8-9)
  - Correspondence, Larry Warford, Assistant to the President, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 9/1-11, 10/1-4)
  - Correspondence, Complaints, 1987-88 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Correspondence, Compliments, 1988 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Correspondence, Condolences, 1988 (Box-folder 10/7)
- Internal Organizations - College Departments, Committees, and Subject Files, 1971-1990; 13.2 cubic feet, 33 document boxes
  This series contains subject files arranged alphabetically. The subject files concern the president’s interaction with college administrative and instructional departments and college committees. They also include topical files that document the wide variety of issues facing the college, including faculty, classified, and management labor relations, the LCC Foundation, and facilities.
  - Academic Calendar, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Academic Council, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - ACCESS, 1986 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Accreditation, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 11/4-5)
  - Administrative Council, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 11/6-10)
  - Administrative Forum, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Administrative Procedures, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 11/12-18)
  - Administrative Services, Vice-president, 1987 (Box-folder 12/1-2)
  - Adult Basic Education, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Adult Basic Education/High School Completion, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Adult Education, 1988 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Advertising/Communication, 1985 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Advisory Committees, 1988 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Agent of Record Committee, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Alcohol Server Education Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Annual Report (President’s), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Apprenticeship, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Art and Applied Design Department, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - ASHLane, 1986 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - ASLCC, 1987 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - ASLCC, Pass the Buck Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Athletic Drivers, 1987 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Athletics, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 12/17,19)
  - Attainment Report (College Plan), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 13/1-4)
  - Audit, Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 13/5-7)
  - Audit Report, 1988 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Audit Reports, SFA Programs, KLCC-FM, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Ballot Measures, 1986 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Bank Signatures, 1987 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Board of Education, Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 14/3-5)
  - Board of Education, Agenda Revisions, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Board of Education, Retreat, 1986 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Board of Education, Executive and Work Sessions, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 14/8-12)
  - Board of Education, Legal, 1988 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Board of Education, Weekly Updates, 1986 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Board of Education, Potential Members, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Board of Education, Members, Mae Westfall Cook, Charlene Curry, Martin Lewis, William, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 15/1-7)
  - Bookstore, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Budget, Budget Committee, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 15/9-16, 16/1-6)
  - Budget Cuts, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Business Affairs, 1986 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Business Assistance Center, 1986 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Business Department, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Business Department, Computers, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Campus Ministries, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Capital Outlay, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 17/6-8)
  - Central Area Education Center, 1986 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Certificate of Appreciation, 1988 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Chinese Exchange, Fellowship Specialist, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Chinese Project, 1986 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Christiansen Resort, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - City of Eugene, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - City of Springfield, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Classified Staff Award, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 17/12-15)
  - Classified/Support Staff Award, 1989 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Classified Training and Development Committee, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Classline, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Classroom Buildings, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Club Wholesale Membership, 1987 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - College Hearings Committee, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - College High Agreements, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - College High Program, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - College Information Day, 1985 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - College Memberships, 1985 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - College Plan, Final Attainment Report, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 18/10-11)
  - College Planning, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Commencement, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 18/13-15)
  - Committees and Councils, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Compensation Survey, 1986 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Complaints, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 19/2-5)
  - Comprehensive Program Review, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Computer Conference, 1986 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Computer Coordinating Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Computer Mainframe, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Computer Networking, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Computer Repair Agreement, 1987 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Computer Services Department, 1987 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Computers, Computer Service, 1988 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Computers, Data Processing, 1987 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Consolation Letters, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Cooperative Work Experience, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Cost/FTE, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Current Costs Per FTE Study, 1987 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Customized Training, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Dean Job Descriptions, 1986 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Degree Requirements, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Dental Accreditation, 1984 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Departmental Planning Packet, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Disabled Students, 1987 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Dislocated Worker Program, 1987 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Drug Abuse, 1986 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Early Retirement, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 20/14-15)
  - Economic Impact Study, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 20/16-17)
  - Elections, 1987 (Box-folder 20/18, 21/1-2)
  - Electronic Mail, 1987 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Electronics Department, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Employee, Management, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Employee Relations, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Energy Management, 1985 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - English Department, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - English, Foreign Languages, Speech, 1988 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Evening College, 1986 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Events, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 21/11-18)
  - EWEB, Buildings, 1987 (Box-folder 21/19)
  - Facilities, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Facilities Construction Fund, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Facilities Five-Year Plan, 1988 (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Facilities Maintenance, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Facilities Management Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Faculty Appointments, 1988 (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Faculty Credentials, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1988 (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Faculty Exchange Programs, 1988 (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Faculty Level Change Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Faculty Workload, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 22/11-12)
  - Fall Welcome Committee, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Financial Aid, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Financial Aid Audit, 1986 (Box-folder 23/2-4)
  - Financial Aid Packaging Agreements, 1986 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Fire Standards and Accreditation Board, 1987 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Flight Technology, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Food Services, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Forestry Program, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Forum Building, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 23/10)
  - Foundation, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 23/11-12, 24/1-3)
  - Foundation, Board of Trustees, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 23/13, 24/4)
  - Foundation, College-Wide Wish List, 1985 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Foundation, Director Search, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Foundation, Evergreen Aviation, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 24/7)
  - Foundation, Gifts, 1988 (Box-folder 24/8)
  - Foundation, Harriet Martin Donation, 1988 (Box-folder 24/9)
  - Foundation, Reports, 1988 (Box-folder 24/10)
  - Foundation, Eldon Schafer Endowment, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 24/11)
  - Foundation, Wayne Shields Endowment, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - FTE Projections, 1987 (Box-folder 24/13)
  - General Committees, 1986 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Graduation, 1987 (Box-folder 25/1-2)
  - Grant Steering Committee, 1987 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Hakanson, Bud, Consultant Request, 1985 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Hakanson, John, Proposal, 1985 (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Hazard Communication Rules Task Force, 1985 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Health Occupations, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 25/8-9)
  - Health Physical Education, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 25/10-12)
  - Hearings Committee, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 25/13)
  - High School Completion Tuition, 1986 (Box-folder 25/14)
  - High School Relations, 1988 (Box-folder 25/15)
  - Hiring Procedures, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 25/16)
  - Huang, Frank, University of Oregon doctoral student, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 25/17-18)
  - Idea Exchange Committee, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 25/19)
  - Industrial Tech, 1987 (Box-folder 25/20)
  - Information Task Force, 1989 (Box-folder 25/21)
  - Inservice, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 26/1-5)
  - Institutional Advancement, 1988 (Box-folder 26/6)
  - Institutional Research, Planning, and Evaluation (IREP), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 26/7-8)
  - IREP, Student Follow-Up Report, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - IREP, Ten-Year Student Enrollment Characteristics, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Instruction, Office of, 1988 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Instruction Reorganization, Alternative Model, 1986 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Instructional Departments, Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Instructional Committee, Goals and Priorities, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Instructional Senate, Inservice, 1985 (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Instructor of the Year, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Instructors, Part-Time, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Insurance Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - International Education, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - International Education Committee, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 27/13)
  - International Education Exchange, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - International Student Exchange Program, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Japan, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Japanese Visit, 1987 (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Job Descriptions, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 27/18-19)
  - KLCC-FM, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 28/1-4)
  - KLCC, Advisory Committee, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 28/5)
  - KLCC, Manager Search, 1987 (Box-folder 28/6-7)
  - KLCC, Siporin, Alan, 1986 (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Labor Relations, 1988 (Box-folder 28/9)
  - Landscaping, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 28/10)
  - Lane Transit District, 1988 (Box-folder 28/11)
  - LCC Bus/Mobile Classroom, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 28/12)
  - LCC, Cottage Grove, 1988 (Box-folder 28/13)
  - LCC, Downtown Center, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 28/14-15)
  - LCC, Downtown Center, Remodeling, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 28/16)
  - LCC, Downtown Center, Tech Center, 1980 (Box-folder 28/17)
  - LCC, Florence, 1988 (Box-folder 28/18)
  - LCCEA, Agreements, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 29/1)
  - LCCEA, Board, 1986 (Box-folder 29/2)
  - LCCEA, Contract, 1987 (Box-folder 29/3)
  - LCCEA, Contract Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 43/15-16)
  - LCCEA, Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 29/4-5)
  - LCCEA, Fact Finding, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 29/6-8)
  - LCCEA, Labor, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 29/9)
  - LCCEA, Negotiations, 1988 (Box-folder 29/10)
  - LCCEF, 1988 (Box-folder 29/11)
  - LCCEF, Agreement, 1987 (Box-folder 30/1)
  - LCCEF, Correspondence, Agreements, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 30/2)
  - LCCEF, Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 30/3)
  - LCCEF, General, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 30/4)
  - LCCEF, Classified Contract, 1986 (Box-folder 30/5)
  - LCC Levy, 1987 (Box-folder 30/6-7)
  - Leaders of the 80s, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 30/8-10)
  - Leaders of the 80s, Marie Matsen, Library Project, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 30/11)
  - Leaders, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 30/12-13)
  - Leadership Eugene-Springfield, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 30/14)
  - Legislature, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 31/1-2)
  - Legislature, Larry Campbell, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Library Computer Project, Marie Matsen, League Leaders Project, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Literacy Coalition, 1988 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Local Elections, 1986 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Management, 1988 (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Management Agreement, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Management Development Funds, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 31/9-11)
  - Management Employees, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 32/1-2)
  - Management Employees Agreement, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 32/3, 32/6-15)
  - Management Employees, Early Retirement Proposal, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 32/4-5)
  - Management Forums, 1987 (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Management Personal Development, 1988 (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Management Personal Development Fund, 1985 (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Management Personal Development Leave Committee, 1986 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Management Placement Review Committee, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 33/5-7)
  - Management Professional Development and Leave Committee, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 33/8-9)
  - Management Salary and Benefits, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Management Salary Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 33/11)
  - Management Steering Committee, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 33/12)
  - Management Step Placement Guidelines, 1986 (Box-folder 33/13)
  - Marketing, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 34/1-4)
  - Marketing Council, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Marketing Plan, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 34/6-7)
  - Marketing Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Marketing Report, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 34/9-10)
  - Marketing Survey, 1983, 1988 (Box-folder 34/11)
  - Martin Luther King Celebration, 1987 (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Massingale, Wendi, 1988 (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Mathematics, 1987 (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Mechanics Department, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 35/4-5)
  - Media Commissions, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Memberships, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Multicultural Center, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35/8)
  - National Community College Month, 1987 (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Needs Assessment, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 35/10)
  - New Employee Orientation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35/11)
  - New Hires, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35/12)
  - News Articles, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 35/13)
  - Nursing, 1987 (Box-folder 35/14)
  - Office World, 1988 (Box-folder 35/16)
  - Oregon Foundation Directors, 1987 (Box-folder 35/18)
  - Oregon State Funding, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 35/19)
  - Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, Dennis Lueck, 1986 (Box-folder 35/17)
  - Other Community Colleges, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 35/15, 36/1)
  - Outlook, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Outreach Program, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Palestinian Visitors, 1987 (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Parking, Downtown Center, 1988 (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Pearl Buck Center, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Performing Arts, 1987 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Personnel, 1987 (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Personnel, Classified Bargaining, Hank Douda, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 43/17)
  - Personnel, Exit Interview Procedures, 1986 (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Personnel, Reclassification, Reductions, 1988 (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Personnel, Recommendations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Personnel, Transfer Procedures, 1987 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Phi Beta Lambda, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Piercy, Jim, 1986 (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Planning, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 36/15-16)
  - Planning Committee, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 37/1-2)
  - Planning Notebook, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 37/3-5)
  - Planning Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 37/6-7)
  - President’s Cabinet, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 37/8-12)
  - President’s Calendar, 1988 (Box-folder 37/13)
  - President’s Evaluation/Personnel Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Printing and Graphics, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 38/1-2)
  - Productivity Funds Use, IREP, 1988 (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Professional Development, Faculty, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Professional Development Leave, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Proposed Teacher Exchange, 1986 (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Public Relations, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Public Relations, Press Conference, 1986 (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Purchasing, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 38/9)
  - Quality Circles, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 38/10)
  - Reorganization, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 38/11-12)
  - Reports, Mid-Year Attainment, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 38/13)
  - Resignations, 1987 (Box-folder 38/14)
  - Retention Task Force, 1986 (Box-folder 38/15)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1986-1989 (Box-folder 38/16)
  - Retirements, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 38/17)
  - Retrenchment, Reduction in Work Force, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 38/18-20)
  - Retrenchment, 1987 (Box-folder 39/1-3)
  - Riepe, Linda, Business Plan, 1986 (Box-folder 39/4)
  - Risk Management, 1987 (Box-folder 39/5)
  - Roofing Study, 1986 (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Rotary Scholarship, 1988 (Box-folder 39/7)
  - ROTC, 1988 (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Safety, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Salaries, 1984 (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Salary Schedule, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Salary Survey, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Sales Tax, 1985 (Box-folder 39/13)
  - Scheduling, 1986 (Box-folder 39/14)
  - School Closure Policy, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 39/15)
  - Science, 1987 (Box-folder 39/16)
  - Security, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 39/17)
  - Self-Support Analysis, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 39/18)
  - Semester Conversion, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 40/1-4)
  - Senior Companion Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Shields, Wayne, 1987 (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Short-Term Training Committee for Faculty, 1988 (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Sister Cities, Soviet, Japan, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 40/8-9)
  - Siuslaw Skills Center, 1986 (Box-folder 40/10)
  - Small Business Development Center, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 40/11-12)
  - Social Science, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 40/13)
  - Special Events, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Special Fees, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41/2)
  - Staff Development Committee, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Staff Development Planning, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Staff Reductions, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Stationery Committee, 1985 (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Stewart, Loran L. (Stub), 1985 (Box-folder 41/7)
  - Student Enrollment, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 41/8)
  - Student Follow-Up, 1987 (Box-folder 41/9)
  - Student Records, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 41/10)
  - Student Retention, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 41/11)
  - Student Retention Committee, 1986 (Box-folder 41/12)
  - Students, 1987 (Box-folder 41/13-14)
  - Substance Abuse Task Force, 1988 (Box-folder 41/15)
  - Surveys, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 41/16-18)
  - Synapse, 1988 (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Targeted Training Network, 1986 (Box-folder 42/1)
  - Teaching Improvement Process, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 42/2)